Guide to the Robert Flaherty Film Seminar Archive 1949 - 2011 MSS.326
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Flaherty Film Seminars
  - Subseries A: Audio Recordings
    - 31st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, August 11, 1985; ID: 326.0413 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0413)
      Original Number: 1985-03
      "Freckled Rice", "A Quite Ordinary Life", "Wild Rose"
    - 31st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 4, August 11, 1985; ID: 326.0414 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0414)
      Original Number: 1985-04
      Wild Rose, Le Denier Glacier
    - 31st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, August 12, 1985; ID: 326.0415 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0415)
      Original Number: 1985-05
      "Le Dernier Glacier", "Vacant Lot", "Sewing Woman", "Living At Risk"
    - 31st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, 1985; ID: 326.0416 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0416)
      Original Number: 1985-06
      "Living At Risk", "The Store Next Door", "Fish Market", "Private Practices"
    - 31st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, August 12, 1985; ID: 326.0417 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0417)
      Original Number: 1985-07
      "Private Practices", "Making Overtures", "Joint Custody"
    - 31st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 8, August 12, 1985; ID: 326.0418 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0418)
      Original Number: 1985-08
      "Joint Custody", "When the Mountains Tremble", "On the Border: American Journey"
    - 31st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, August 12, 1985; ID: 326.0419 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0419)
      Original Number: 1985-09
      When the Mountains Tremble, On the Border: An American Journey, The Revolt of Job
    - 31st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, August 14, 1985; ID: 326.0420 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0420)
      Original Number: 1985-10
      The Revolt of Job, Witness to War
    - 31st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, August 14, 1985; ID: 326.0421 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0421)
      Original Number: 1985-11
      Paul Cadmus: Enfant, Terrible at 80, Reuben Nakian: Apprentice to the Gods, We were so beloved, Manny Kirchheimer
    - 31st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, August 14, 1985; ID: 326.0422 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0422)
      Original Number: 1985-12
      We were so beloved, Acceptable levels,
      The race against prime time
    - 31st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13, August 15, 1985; ID: 326.0423 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0423)
      Original Number: 1985-13
      The race against prime time,
      The homeless,
      The Mexican tapes
    - 31st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 14, August 15, 1985; ID: 326.0424 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0424)
      Original Number: 1985-14
      One Amish,
      Start [let ye inheret]
    - 31st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, August 16, 1985; ID: 326.0425 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0425)
      Original Number: 1985-15
      Growing up with rockets,
      Maids and Madams,
      The Amish: Not to be modern
    - 31st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 16, August 16, 1985; ID: 326.0426 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0426)
      Original Number: 1985-16
      Let ye inheret,
      The killing floor
    - 31st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 17, August 16, 1985; ID: 326.0427 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0427)
      Original Number: 1985-17
      The killing floor, Bill Duke,
      Growing up with rockets, Nancy Yasecko
    - 31st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 18, August 17,1985; ID: 326.0428 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0428)
      Original Number: 1985-18
      Deadhead,
      Wrap-up discussion
    - 32nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 1, August 9, 1986; ID: 326.0429 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0429)
      Original Number: 1986-01
      "Shadows on the Future" Wolfganag Bergman,
      Moderator: Deac Russell,
      Opening Night
    - 32nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, Augusst 10, 1986; ID: 326.0430 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0430)
      Original Number: 1986-03
      "Naked Spaces" Trinh T. Minh Ha, "Troubled Waters" John Hanson,
      Moderator: Bill Sloan, Juan Mandelbaum, also B. Sloan, B. Van Dyke, A. Lamont, or W. Van Dyke
    - 32nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 4, August 10, 1986; ID: 326.0431 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0431)
      Original Number: 1986-04
      "Made in China" Lisa Hsia, Patrick Amos on Gorin film "Positive Pleasures",
      Discussion: Lisa Hsia and Patrick Amos, Moderator: Steven Scheuer, Group Introductions
    - 32nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, August 10, 1986; ID: 326.0432 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0432)
      Original Number: 1986-05
      Lisa Hsia and Patrick Amos,
      Discussion on Willand Van Dyke,
      Video: Latin American TV, Karen Renacci
    - 32nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, August 11, 1986; ID: 326.0433 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0433)
      Original Number: 1986-06
      Latin American TV, Karen Ranucci, Moderator: Juan Mandelbaum,
      "All American High" Keva Rosenfeld, Moderator: Deirdra Baylen, "Orientations" Richard Fung, Moderator: Pearl Bowser
    - 32nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, August 11, 1986; ID: 326.0434 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0434)
      Original Number: 1986-07
      "Orientations" Richard Fung,
      "30 second spots" Joan Logue, Moderator: Dorothy Olson,
      Beginning discussion with King Ampau, "Kukurantumi: Road to Accra", Moderator: Tony Gittens
    - 32nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 8, August 11, 1986; ID: 326.0435 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0435)
      Original Number: 1986-08
      "Kukurantumi: Road to Accra", King Ampau continued,
      Moderator: Tony Gittens,
      Evening: Twenty Years Later, Eduardo Coatinho, Moderator: George Stoney
    - 32nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, August 12, 1986; ID: 326.0436 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0436)
      Original Number: 1986-09
      "Twenty Years Later", Eduardo Courtinho, Moderator: George Stoney
    - 32nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, August 12, 1986; ID: 326.0437 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0437)
      Original Number: 1986-11
      Jon Alpert continued,
      "Itam Hakim Hopit", Hopi Tapas, Victor Maseyara, Moderator: Deirdre Boyle
    - 32nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, August 12, 1986; ID: 326.0438 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0438)
      Original Number: 1986-12
      Victor Maseyesra, Moderator: Deirdre Boyle,
      Twin Cities Video, Helen De Michiel, Moderator: Dorothy D. Olsen
    - 32nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13, August 13, 1986; ID: 326.0439 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0439)
      Original Number: 1986-13
      "Indian Cabaret" Mira Nair, Moderator: Esme Dick,
      "Rate it X", Lucy Winer, Moderator: Tony Gittens
    - 32nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 14, August 13, 1986; ID: 326.0440 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0440)
      Original Number: 1986-14
      Rate it X - cont'd Winer,
      "Sounds" + Jaime Barrios,
      mod. Linda Blackaby
    - 32nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, August 14, 1986; ID: 326.0441 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0441)
      "Central America Comes to Middle America",
      Martha Wallner,
      Mod. Tony Gittens,
      "To Taste a Hundred Herbs",
      Carma Hinton, Richard Gordon,
      Mod. Eome Dick
      Original Number: 1986-15
    - 32nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 16, August 14, 1986; ID: 326.0442 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0442)
      Original Number: 1986-16
      "To Tase a Hundred Herbs",
      Carma Hinton cont'd,
      eve. "Forest of Bliss",
      Robert Gardner,
      mod. Deac Rossell
    - 32nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 17, August 14-15, 1986; ID: 326.0443 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0443)
      Original Number: 1986-17
      8-14-86:
      "Forest of Bliss", Robert Gardner cont'd,
      8-15-86:
      "The Aids Show", Peter Adair, mod. Linda Blackaby
    - 32nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 18, August 15, 1986; ID: 326.0444 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0444)
      Original Number: 1986-18
      "The AIDS Show," Peter Adair, 3. Sweethearts of Rhythm, Gretta Schiller, Andrea Weiss, Moderator Linda Blackaby,
      Didea "B, 2 songs of wool, Cathy Edwards, Anthony Gittens
    - 32nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 19, undated; ID: 326.0445 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0445)
      Original Number: 1986-19
      Sweethearts of Rhythm, Jeff Skoller, Gretta Schiller, Andrea Weiss,
      A Weave of Time, Susan Fanshell, Deborah Gordon (moderator Anthony Gittens)
    - 32nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 20, undated; ID: 326.0446 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0446)
      Original Number: 1986-20
      Jeff Skoller,
      (moderator: Anthony Gittens),
      "Drive-In Blues," Jawkravitz,
      (moderator: Anthony Gittens)
    - 33rd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 1, August 9, 1987; ID: 326.0447 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0447)
      Original Number: 1987-01
      1987 Robert Flaherty Film Seminar Tape,
      Date: 8/9/87, Time: 10-12, Film/Videomake: Phil Jones
    - 33rd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 4, August 10, 1987; ID: 326.0448 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0448)
      Original Number: 1987-04
      Date: 8/10/1987,
      Film/Video: Gianikian,
      Film/Video Maker: ¶ Director,
      Moderator: Scott McDonald
    - 33rd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, August 10, 1987; ID: 326.0449 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0449)
      Original Number: 1987-05
      1987 Robert Flaherty Seminar Tape #5,
      Date: 8/10/87,
      Time: 9:20 p.m.
      Film/Video: "The Africans",
      Film/Videomaker: Charles Hobson,
      Moderator: Pearl Bowser
    - 33rd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, August 11, 1987; ID: 326.0450 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0450)
      Original Number: 1987-06
      1987 Robert Flaherty Seminar Tape #6,
      Date: 8/11/87
      Time: Morning
      Film/Video: Linda Rarpel
      Film/Video Maker: Han Ziv co-producer/director Consuming Hunger
      Moderator: Bill Sloan
    - 33rd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, October 11, 1987; ID: 326.0451 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0451)
      Original Number: 1987-07
      1987 Robert Flaherty Seminar Tape #7
      Date: 10/11/87
      Film/Video: Handswarth Soup / The Bone Giy of OSay e Avenue
      Film/Video maker: John Akonfrah / Louis Wassiah
    - 33rd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 8, August 11, 1987; ID: 326.0452 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0452)
      Original Number: 1987-08
      1987 Robert Flaherty Seminar Tape
      Film/Video: Bawdung File
      Film/Video Maker: Darcus Howe
      Moderator: Wawda Bershen
    - 33rd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, August 12, 1987; ID: 326.0453 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0453)
      Original Number: 1987-09
      Film/Video Maker: Johan van der Keuken
    - 33rd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, August 12, 1987; ID: 326.0454 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0454)
      Original Number: 1987-10
      Film/Video: The Journey
      Film/Video Maker: Peter Watkins
    - 33rd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, August 12, 1987; ID: 326.0455 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0455)
      Original Number: 1987-11
    - 33rd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, August 13, 1987; ID: 326.0456 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0456)
      Original Number: 1987-12
      Film/Video: The Ties That Bind Damned If You Don't
      Film/Video Maker: Su Friedrich
      Moderator: Richard Herskowitz
    - 33rd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13, August 13, 1987; ID: 326.0457 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0457)
      Original Number: 1987-13
      Film/Video: Coming of Age
      Film/Video Maker: Marc Huestis
    - 33rd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 14, August 13, 1987; ID: 326.0458 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0458)
      Original Number: 1987-14
      Video: Ads Epidemic The Perils of Pedagogy The Jungle Boy Kipling Meets the Cowboys Moscow Does Not Believe in Queers
      Film/Video Maker: John Greyson
    - 33rd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, August 13, 1987; ID: 326.0459 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0459)
      Original Number: 1987-15
      Film/Video: Tabu - Intro and Questions
      Film/Video Maker: Mark Langer
    - 33rd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 16, August 14, 1987; ID: 326.0460 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0460)
      Original Number: 1987-16
      Film/Video: Don't Start Talking to Me Maggie & the Men of Minnesota Mickey's Diner
      Film/Video Maker: Stevenson Palfi, Deanna Kamiel, Richard Herskowitz
      The Way South Johann Vanderkeuken
    - 33rd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 17, August 14, 1987; ID: 326.0461 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0461)
      Original Number: 1987-17
      Film/Video: The Way South
      Film/Video Maker: Johann Vanderkeuken
      Tami Gold - Prescription for Change: (From Bedside to Bargaining Table), Looking for Love: Teenage Parents
      Pamela Yates - Who Are the Contras?, I'll Vote on We're Not Gonna Take It
    - 33rd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 18, August 14, 1987; August 15, 1987; ID: 326.0462 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0462)
      Original Number: 1987-18
      Film/Video: Prescription for Change Looking for Love Who Are the Contras? I'll Vote On We're Not Gonna Take It
      Film/Video Maker: Tami Gold, Pamela Yates
      Saturday, August 15, 1987: Wrap up discussion
    - 33rd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 19, August 13, 1987; August 15, 1987; ID: 326.0463 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0463)
      Original Number: 1987-19
      08/13/1987: Mark Heustes (15 minutes)
      08/15/1987: Seminar Wrap Up Discussion
    - 34th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 1, August 13, 1988; ID: 326.0464 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0464)
      Original Number: 1988-01
      General Intro Tony Buba
    - 34th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 2, August 13, 1988; ID: 326.0465 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0465)
      Original Number: 1988-02
      End of Introductions Start of Sharon Greytak
      Title: Girl Talk
      Moderator: Linda Blackaby
      Film/Video Maker: Kate Davis
    - 34th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, August 14, 1988; ID: 326.0466 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0466)
      Original Number: 1988-03
      Title(s): Weirded Out, Blown Away
      Film/Video Maker(s): Sharon Greytak, Mira Hamermesh
    - 34th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 4, August 14, 1988; ID: 326.0467 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0467)
      Original Number: 1988-04
      End of Mira Hamermesh
      Title: Out of the Mouths of Babes
      Film/Video Maker(s): Sherry Millner, Ernest Larsen
    - 34th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, August 14, 1988; August 15, 1988; ID: 326.0468 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0468)
      Original Number: 1988-05
      Moderator: Ho Film/Video Maker: Dennis O'Rourke
      Moderator: Louis Massiah Film/Video Maker: Robert Crusz
      Moderator: Grant Munro Film/Video Maker: Jonathan Amitay
    - 34th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, August 15, 1988; ID: 326.0469 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0469)
      Original Number: 1988-06
      Moderator: Jack Churchill Film/Video Maker: Dennis O'Rourke
    - 34th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, August 15, 1988; ID: 326.0470 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0470)
      Original Number: 1988-07
      Title: Zina
      Moderator: Juan Mandelbaum
      Film/Video Maker: Ken McMullen
    - 34th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 8, August 16, 1988; ID: 326.0471 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0471)
      Original Number: 1988-08
      Moderator: Julie Jerenson; Juan Mendelbaum
      Film/Video Maker(s): Lise Yasui, Ann Teghell, Richard Fung, Stephen Roswell, Leslie Thornton, Margot Starr
    - 34th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, August 16, 1988; ID: 326.0472 (Box 10, Media ID: 326.0472)
      Original Number: 1988-09
      Moderator(s): Tom Johnson; Louis Massiah
      Film/Video Maker: Margot Starr; Rob Nilsson
    - 34th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, August 17, 1988; ID: 326.0473 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0473)
      Original Number: 1988-10
      Moderator: Louis Massiah
      Film/Video Maker(s): Rob Nielsson; P. Rose
    - 34th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, August 18, 1988; ID: 326.0474 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0474)
      Original Number: 1988-11
      Title: This Is Our Home It Is Not For Sale
      Film/Video Maker: Jon Schwartz
    - 34th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, August 18, 1988; ID: 326.0475 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0475)
      Original Number: 1988-12
      Title: Inside Life Outside Moderator: Jack Churchill Film/Video Maker: Sinkler and Harnada
      Title: Older Woman & Jealous Bone Moderator: Julie Levinson Film/Video Maker: Billops and Condit
    - 34th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13, August 18, 1988; ID: 326.0476 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0476)
      Original Number: 1988-13
      8/18/1988, 10:00pm Title: Bless Their Little Hearts Moderator: Blackaby Film/Video Maker: Woodberry
      8/19/1988: Title: Beirut: The Last Home Movie Moderator: Johnson Film/Video Maker: Jennifer Fox
    - 34th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 14, August 19, 1988; ID: 326.0477 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0477, Box Shared Fales 134, Cd 326.0477_pt.1, Cd 326.0477_pt.2)
      Original Number: 1988-14
      Title(s): The Motherland; Partition; The Laughing Alligator
      Moderator(s): Juan Mandelbaum; Ken McMullen
      Film/Video Maker(s): Juan Downey; Julie Levinson
    - 34th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, August 19, 1988; ID: 326.0478 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0478, Box Shared Fales 134, Cd 326.0478)
      Original Number: 1988-15
      Title(s): 1. Partition 2. Cannibal Tours
      Moderator(s): 1. Julie Levinson 2. Tom Johnson
      Film/Video Maker(s): 1. Ken McMullen 2. Dennis O'Rourke
    - 34th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 16, August 19, 1988; ID: 326.0479 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0479)
      Original Number: 1988-16
      Title: Cannibal Tours Moderator: Tom Johnson Film/Video Maker: Dennis O'Rourke
    - 34th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 17, August 20, 1988; ID: 326.0480 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0480)
      Original Number: 1988-17
      Closing Discussion Moderator(s): Julie, Barbara, Jack and the whole bunch
    - 36th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 1, June 10, 1990; ID: 326.0481 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0481)
      Original Number: 1990-01
      6/10/90 AM: Moderator: Richard Peterson Artist: Robert Thurber
      6/10/90 PM: Moderator: Richard Peterson Artists: Tom Johnson, Rick Prelinger
    - 36th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 2, June 10, 1990; ID: 326.0482 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0482)
      Original Number: 1990-02
      Moderator: Richard Peterson Artist: Rick Prelinger
    - 36th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, June 10, 1990; ID: 326.0483 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0483)
      Original Number: 1990-03
      Moderator: Richard Peterson Artists: Mary Jimenez, Francoise Romand
    - 36th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 4, June 11, 1990; ID: 326.0484 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0484)
      Original Number: 1990-04
      Moderator: Lise Yasui Artist: Indu Krishnah
      Moderator: Richard Peterson Artist: Walter Brock
      Moderator: Bo Smith Artist: Mary Jimenez
    - 36th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, June 11, 1990; ID: 326.0485 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0485)
      Original Number: 1990-05
      Moderator: Richard Peterson Artist: Christian Blackwood
    - 36th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, June 12, 1990; ID: 326.0486 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0486)
      Original Number: 1990-06
      Moderator: O [Funmilayo] Makarah Artist: Vana lyne Green moderator: Mary Lee Bandy Artist: Francoise Romand
    - 36th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, June 12, 1990; ID: 326.0487 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0487)
      Original Number: 1990-07
      Artist: Jayne Loader with her piece Moderator: Richard Peterson (Rick Prelinger)
    - 36th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 8, June 12, 1990; ID: 326.0488 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0488)
      Original Number: 1990-08
      Moderator: Richard Peterson Artist: Jayne Loader
      Moderator: Richard peterson Artist: Chuck Workman
    - 36th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, June 13, 1990; ID: 326.0489 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0489)
      Original Number: 1990-09
      Moderator: Bo Smith Artist: Ellen Bruno
      Moderator: Bill Sloan Artist: Gary Pollard
      Moderator: Christine McDonald Artist: Su Friedrich
    - 36th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, June 13, 1990; ID: 326.0490 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0490)
      Original Number: 1990-10
      Moderator: John Columbus Artist: Patti Bruck
      Moderator: Sally Berger Artist: Marlon Riggs
    - 36th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, June 14, 1990; ID: 326.0491 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0491)
      Original Number: 1990-11
      Moderator: Jay Ruby John katz on Flaherty, "The Land"
      Moderator: Jay Ruby Artist: Maria de Luca
    - 36th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, June 14, 1990; ID: 326.0492 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0492)
      Original Number: 1990-12
      Moderator: [Dean] Rossel Artist: Jim Klein, Susan Wehling
    - 36th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13, June 15, 1990; ID: 326.0493 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0493)
      Original Number: 1990-13
      Moderator: Bill Rowley Artist: Pola Rapaport
      Moderator: Lucy Kostelelanctz Artist: Robert Thurber
    - 36th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 14, June 15, 1990; ID: 326.0494 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0494)
      Original Number: 1990-14
      Moderator: Lucy [Kostelelanctz] Artist: Robert Thurber
      Moderator: Lisa [Yasui] Artist: Janice Tanaka
      Moderator: Alan Rosenthal Artists: Elizabeth Taylor Mead, Nicholas Dubrule
      Discussion: Bo Smith, Richard Peterson, John Katz
    - 36th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, June 15, 1990; ID: 326.0495 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0495)
      Original Number: 1990-15
      Moderator Bo Smith Artist: Gyula Gazdag
      Discussion Moderator: Tom Johnson
    - 36th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 16, June 16, 1990; ID: 326.0496 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0496)
      Original Number: 1990-16
      Final Discussion Moderator: Tom Johnson
    - 37th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 1, August 3, 1991; ID: 326.0497 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0497)
      Original Number: 1991-01
      "Auffengeil" Moderator: Richard Herkowitz Guests: Coco Fusco, Steve Gallager
      "Body Beautiful" "Desperate" Moderator: Coco Fusco
    - 37th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 2, August 4, 1991; ID: 326.0498 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0498)
      Original Number: 1991-02
    - 37th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, August 5, 1991; ID: 326.0499 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0499)
      Original Number: 1991-03
      New Brazilian Shorts Guests: Joao Luiz Vieira
      "Camera Arabe" Moderator: Steve Gallagher Guests: Ella Shohat
    - 37th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 4, August 5, 1991; ID: 326.0500 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0500)
      Original Number: 1991-04
      "A Door is The Sky" Moderator: Coco Fusco Guests: Viola Shafir
      "Sights Unseen" "Work In Progress" "Un Chien Delicieux" "Tribulation 99" Moderator: Coco Fusco Guests: Luis Valdovino, Jonathan Robinson, Craig Baldwin, Ken Feingold
    - 37th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, August 5, 1991; ID: 326.0501 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0501)
      Original Number: 1991-05
      "Chien Delivieux" "Space & Time" "Door To The Sky" Moderator: Faye Ginsberg Roddy Bogawa- "Some Divine Wind Rea [Tiddiri]- "History and Memory"
    - 37th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, August 5, 1991; ID: 326.0502 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0502)
      Original Number: 1991-06
      "History & Memory" "Some Divine Wind" Moderator: Faye Ginsburg Guests: Red Tajliri, Roddy Bogwawa
      "Permissible Dreams" "Omar Gatlato" Moderator: Coco Fusco Guests: Viola Alia Arasoughly
    - 37th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, August 6, 1991; ID: 326.0503 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0503)
      Original Number: 1991-07
      "Once Upon a Time in the Bronx" "Rap City Rhapsody" "Fade to Black" Moderator: Steve Gallagher Guests: Ela Troyano, Don Trammel
      "Urinal" "The Making of 'Monsters'" Guests: John Greyson
    - 37th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 8, August 6, 1991; ID: 326.0504 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0504)
      Original Number: 1991-08
      Introduction & "Louisiana Story" by Bill Sloan
    - 37th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, August 6, 1991; ID: 326.0505 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0505)
      Original Number: 1991-09
      "Making of 'Monsters'" "Urinal" Guests: John Greyson
      "Fertile Memories" Moderator: Ella Shohat, Viola Shafik
    - 37th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, August 7, 1991; ID: 326.0506 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0506)
      Original Number: 1991-10